{
    "id": "aa64539677064b4c98198c2561740e44",
    "title": "Good and well exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "adff4451dd55455eafd630a024480194",
            "title": "Good And Well Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "That was a …………………… film.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She speaks Chinese …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The steak smells …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My new car runs …………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She sings really ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "well",
                        "good"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I admire her. She is a ………………… writer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her English is very …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The holiday did me a lot of …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "They gave me some ………………….. advice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We think …………………… of him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "well"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}